Guide to the Laura Foreman Papers 1949-2001 MSS.122
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Correspondence, 6.25 Linear Feet 5 Paige Cartons
  Series III contains correspondence, most of which was written to Foreman by her mother, Gladys Foreman. In addition to personal correspondence, a small portion of this series pertains to Foreman's art, writing and teaching.
  This series is arranged chronologically, with an emphasis on preserving Foreman's original arrangement. Because original arrangement was the main processing concern, there are small chronological overlaps from folder to folder (e.g. a folder dated "1986-89" may be followed by one dated "1987-88"). There is no chronological overlap between boxes in the series.
  - Correspondence, 1949-1960 (Box 84)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718579
  - Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 85)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718587
  - Correspondence, 1965-1975 (Box 86)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718595
  - Correspondence, 1976-1988 (Box 87)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718603
  - Correspondence, 1989-2000, undated (Box 88)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142050718611
- Series IV: Photographic Material, 5.65 Linear Feet 27 photo binders
  The photographic material of Series IV spans the entirety of Foreman's career, from early dance performances through later art installations in the nineteen-nineties. Performances from the Laura Foreman Dance Company are very well documented, as are the numerous derivations of Foreman's "Birdhouse as Metaphor" series. Photographers of Foreman's dance performances include Robert Alexander, Peter Moore and Milton Oleaga.
  The photographic material is arranged thematically and chronologically, similarly to the list of works in the Biographical Note above. Stage works are documented first, followed by artworks, followed by specific installations and exhibitions, and concluding with personal and unidentified photos. Each box is annotated with the photographic processes contained within.
  - Freedom Dancers, undated (Box 89)
    Photographic Prints
  - "Solo Suite", 1967 (Box 89)
  - Laura Foreman Dance Company, group and individual shots, 1967-75, undated (Box 89)
    Photographic Prints, Contact Sheets
  - Laura Foreman Dance Company, group and individual shots, 1967-75, undated (Box 90)
  - "A Time", 1968 (Box 90)
  - "Perimeters", 1969 (Box 90)
  - "Untitled", 1970 (Box 90)
  - Kelly Holt's "new trio for Shungopovi Shade", 1970 (Box 90)
  - "Epicycles", 1970 (Box 90)
  - "Signals", 1970 (Box 90)
  - "glass and shadows", 1971 (Box 90)
  - "Laura's Dance", 1971 (Box 91)
  - "Songandance", 1972 (Box 91)
  - "Margins", 1972 (Box 91)
  - "Spaces", 1972-1973 (Box 91)
  - "Locrian", 1973 (Box 91)
  - "Performance", 1973 (Box 91)
  - "city of angels", 1974 (Box 91)
  - "a deux", 1974 (Box 91)
  - "Postludes", 1974 (Box 92)
  - "Bud" / "Monopoly", 1975 (Box 92)
  - "Program", 1976 (Box 92)
  - "Heirlooms", 1977 (Box 92)
  - "Entries", 1978 (Box 92)
  - John Butler's "Portrait of Billie", undated (Box 92)
  - Photographs related to Foreman's Dance Instruction, 1967-71, undated (Box 92)
  - Photos of unidentified events by Composers and Choreographers Theatre, 1971, 1974, undated (Box 93)
    Photographic Prints, Contact Sheets, Black-and-white Negatives
  - "Ken and Barbie" Series, undated (Box 93)
    Polaroids, Color Slides
  - "Birdhouse as Metaphor" Series, 1989-1993 (Box 94)
    Photographic Prints, Color Slides, Color Transparencies, Black-and-white Negatives, Contact Sheets, Polaroids
  - "Birdhouse as Metaphor" Series, 1989-1993 (Box 95)
  - "Birdhouse as Metaphor" Series, 1989-1993 (Box 96)
  - Photos of birdhouses sent to Foreman by a fellow craftsman and admirer of her work, 1993 (Box 96)
    The original mailing envelope and accompanying letter can be found in Series III, Correspondence, Box 88.
  - "Coney Island Cray-Pas", 1981 (Box 97)
    Photographic Prints, Color Slides, Contact Sheets
  - "Cry Uncle", 1991 (Box 97)
    Color Slides, Color Transparencies
  - "Lady Bug Drips" Paintings, undated (Box 98)
    Color Slides
  - "Lady Bug Drips" Paintings, undated (Box 99)
  - "Philadelphia Story", 1981 (Box 99)
  - "Poetry Peep Show", undated (Box 99)
  - "Roomwork", 1981 (Box 100)
    Photographic Prints, Black-and-white Negatives, Color Slides
  - "Sweet Land of Liberty", 1983 (Box 100)
  - "TimeCoded Woman", 1979-1980 (Box 101)
  - "Wallwork", 1981 (Box 101)
    Black-and-white Negatives, Photographic Prints, Contact Sheets, Color Slides
  - "Wallwork", 1981 (Box 102)
  - "Wallwork"in Paris and Stockholm (by John Watts), 1981 (Box 102)
    Color Slides, Photographic Prints, Contact Sheets, Black-and-white Negatives
  - "Window on the World", 1995 (Box 103)
  - "Word Painting" / "I have nothing to paint and I'm painting it.", 1983 (Box 103)
    Photographic Prints, Color Slides, Color Negatives
  - Mixed Media Paintings / Sculpture / Drawings, 1979-1991, undated (Box 103)
    Polaroids, Photographic Prints, Color Slides
  - Mixed Media Paintings / Sculpture / Drawings, 1979-1991, undated (Box 104)
  - Mixed Media Paintings / Sculpture / Drawings, 1979-1991, undated (Box 105)
  - Mixed Media Paintings / Sculpture / Drawings, 1979-1991, undated (Box 106)
  - Mixed Media Paintings / Sculpture / Drawings, 1979-1991, undated (Box 107)
  - Mixed Media Paintings / Sculpture / Drawings, 1979-1991, undated (Box 108)
  - Documentation of Limbo Exhibition, 1984 (Box 108)
  - Documentation of Portico Gallery Installation, 1982 (Box 109)
    Photographic Prints, Contact Sheets, Polaroids, Color Slides, Black-and-white Negatives
  - Documentation of Souyun Yi Gallery Exhibition, 1988 (Box 110)
    Photographic Prints, Color Slides
  - Portraits of Laura Foreman, undated (Box 110)
  - Personal Photos, undated (Box 111)
    Color Negatives, Color Slides, Photographic Prints
  - Personal Photos, undated (Box 112)
  - Portraits and performance photos of John Watts, 1970-71, undated (Box 113)
  - Portraits and performance photos of John Watts, 1970-71, undated (Box 114)
  - Photos of unidentified persons and events, undated (Box 114)
    Black-and-white Negatives, Photographic Prints, Color Slides, Contact Sheets
  - Photos of unidentified persons and events, undated (Box 115)
- Series V: Artworks, Sketches and Posters, 0.83 Linear Feet 2 Document Cases
  Series V contains primarily visual material produced by Foreman, including sketches, drafts, and posters from her own as well as others' performances and exhibitions.
  The materials in Series V are arranged alphabetically by folder title. The majority of the works are untitled. Where posssible, entire sketchbooks are housed intact. Otherwise, materials remain in their original arrangements.
  - Sketchbooks (Box 116, Folder 1-7)
  - Sketchbooks (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
  - Untitled Sketches (Box 117, Folder 3-10)
- Series VI: Video recordings, 1973-1985; 41.25 Linear Feet 33 Paige Cartons
  Conditions Governing Access
  Video recordings have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  Series VI contains Foreman's collection of video documentation of her dance performances and other artworks and exhibitions.
  - Subseries A: Original tapes
    - Fantasy Teddy Bear Shots, 1978; ID: 122.0001 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0001)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      Original format: 3/4 in. Umatic
      Duration: 21 minutes
    - Dummies Reel #1, 1978; ID: 122.0002 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0002)
      Duration: 20 minutes
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Dummies Reel #1
    - Dummies Reel #2, 1978; ID: 122.0003 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0003)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Dummies Reel #2
    - Tape #1 Laura in Prop Room, 1978; ID: 122.0004 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0004)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Prop Room Tape #1
    - Laura in Prop Room, 1978; ID: 122.0005 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0005)
      Currently unavailable.
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Prop Room Tape #2
    - Satoru at Japan House, The Marpetts #1, 1978; ID: 122.0006 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0006)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Dressing Room at Japan House
    - Schtict Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0007 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0007)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Laura Talking To Mirror Tape #1
    - Schtict Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0008 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0008)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Laura Talks to Mirror Tape#2
    - Laura's Schtict Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0009 (Box 118, Media ID: 122.0009)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Laura Talking to Herself
    - Laura's Schtict Tape #4, 1978; ID: 122.0010 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0010)
      Duration: 3 minutes
    - Mirror Shots Tape I, 1978; ID: 122.0011 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0011)
      Alternate Title: Fantasy / Mirror Shots Tape #1
    - Mirror Tape II, 1978; ID: 122.0012 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0012)
    - Poster Shots #1, 1978; ID: 122.0013 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0013)
    - Poster Shots #2, 1978; ID: 122.0014 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0014)
    - 19th St. Shot, 1978; ID: 122.0015 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0015)
    - 19th St. Front Steps and Upstairs, 1978; ID: 122.0016 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0016)
    - Japan House Reel I, 1978; ID: 122.0017 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0017)
    - Japan House Reel II, 1978; ID: 122.0018 (Box 119, Media ID: 122.0018)
    - Japan House Reel III, 1978; ID: 122.0019 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0019)
      Duration: 11 minutes
    - Fantasy Shots Tape 5, 1978; ID: 122.0020 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0020)
      Currently unavailable until duplciation occurs.
    - Fantasy - Playground Tape I, 1978; ID: 122.0021 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0021)
    - Fantasy - Playground Tape II, 1978; ID: 122.0022 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0022)
      Currently unavailable until duplication.
    - Installation #1, 1978; ID: 122.0023 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0023)
    - Installation #2, 1978; ID: 122.0024 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0024)
      Duration: 13 minutes
    - Fantasy Shots of Laura Upstairs, 1978; ID: 122.0025 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0025)
      Currently available until duplication occurs.
    - Poetry Performance Events, 1978; ID: 122.0026 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0026)
      Duration: 10 minutes
    - Poetry Reading Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0027 (Box 120, Media ID: 122.0027)
    - Poetry Reading Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0028 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0028)
    - Mug Shots and Barre Insert Tape #4, 1978; ID: 122.0029 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0029)
    - Mug Shots and Inserts Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0030 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0030)
      Currently available.
    - Arp Room Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0031 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0031)
    - Arp Studio Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0032 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0032)
      Alternate Title: Arp Room Tape #2
    - John Watts in Arp Room, 1978; ID: 122.0033 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0033)
      Alternate Title: Mark Fisher Arp Room Tape #1
    - John Watts in Arp Room #2, 1978; ID: 122.0034 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0034)
      Alternate Title: Mark Fisher Arp Room Tape #2
    - John and Laura in Arp Room #3, 1978; ID: 122.0035 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0035)
      Alternate Title: M.F. Arp Room #3
    - Entries Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0036 (Box 121, Media ID: 122.0036)
    - Entries Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0037 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0037)
      Duration: 12 minutes
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape Reel #2
    - Entries Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0038 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0038)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape Reel #3
    - Tape #1 - Go, Hamlet, Swan Lake, Roof section, 1978; ID: 122.0039 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0039)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #4
    - Tape #2 - Go, Hamlet, Swan Lake, Roof Sequence, 1978; ID: 122.0040 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0040)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #5
    - Tape #3 - Go, Hamlet, Swan Lake, Roof Sequence, 1978; ID: 122.0041 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0041)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #6
    - Tape #4 - Hamlet, 1978; ID: 122.0042 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0042)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #7
    - Fetal Clap #1, 1978; ID: 122.0043 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0043)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #8
    - Fetal Clap #2, 1978; ID: 122.0044 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0044)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #9
    - Fetal Claps #3 and Go, 1978; ID: 122.0045 (Box 122, Media ID: 122.0045)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #10
    - Go #4, 1978; ID: 122.0046 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0046)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #11
    - Go (end) #5, 1978; ID: 122.0047 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0047)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #12
    - Go (end) close ups and Adeux #6, 1978; ID: 122.0048 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0048)
    - Wall Section Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0049 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0049)
      Originally format: 3/4 in. Umatic
      Alternate Title: Enteries Alternate Tape 49A
    - Wall Section Tape #5, 1978; ID: 122.0050 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0050)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #14
    - Wall Secion Tape #4, 1978; ID: 122.0051 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0051)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #15
    - "Enteries" Documentary pt. I Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0052 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0052)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #16
    - "Enteries" Documentary pt. II Tape #5, 1978; ID: 122.0053 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0053)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #17
    - "Enteries" Documentary pt. III Tape 4, 1978; ID: 122.0054 (Box 123, Media ID: 122.0054)
      Alternate Title: Entries Tape #18
    - Rehearsal / Time Piece #1, 1978; ID: 122.0055 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0055)
    - Rehearsal / Time Piece #2, 1978; ID: 122.0056 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0056)
      Duration: 15 minutes
    - Satoru Rehearsing and Laura Watching, 1978; ID: 122.0057 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0057)
      Duration: 30 minutes
    - Satoru's Loft and Laura Jogging, 1978; ID: 122.0058 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0058)
      Alternate Title: Five minutes of Satoru's loft and Laura jogging
    - Construction of 6/78 Dance #1, 1978; ID: 122.0059 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0059)
      Alternate Title: Laura and Satoru and Construction of 6/78 Dance
    - Construction of 6/78 Dance #2, 1978; ID: 122.0060 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0060)
    - Construction of 6/78 Dance #3, 1978; ID: 122.0061 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0061)
    - Satoru Talking About Laura, 1978; ID: 122.0062 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0062)
    - Satoru Rehearsing Wall Dance #1, 1978; ID: 122.0063 (Box 124, Media ID: 122.0063)
      Alternate Title: Wall Dance / Pillar to Post
    - Satoru Rehearsing Wall Dance #2, 1978; ID: 122.0064 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0064)
      Alternate Title: Wall Dance / Pillar to Post #2
    - Hound Dog #2, 1978; ID: 122.0065 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0065)
      Alternate Title: 5/5/78 #2 Fisher SS: Hound Dog
    - Mark Fisher Taping Satoru #3, 1978; ID: 122.0066 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0066)
      Alternate Title: Rehearsal Tape "Sarabande"
    - Rehearsal Hound Dog and 19th Street Shots, 1978; ID: 122.0067 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0067)
    - Mark Fisher Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0068 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0068)
      Alternate Title: "Go" Rehearsal
    - Mark Fisher Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0069 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0069)
    - Mark Fisher Audition Tape, 1978; ID: 122.0070 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0070)
    - Test Tape of Other Deck, 1978; ID: 122.0071 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0071)
      Alternate Title: "Enteries"
    - Laura Foreman Dance Test I, 1978; ID: 122.0072 (Box 125, Media ID: 122.0072)
    - Satoru in Loft Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0073 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0073)
    - Satoru in Loft Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0074 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0074)
    - Satoru Opening Gifts From Japan #1, 1978; ID: 122.0075 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0075)
    - Satoru's Upset and Laura's Response #1, 1978; ID: 122.0076 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0076)
    - Satoru Warming Up at Barre with Clothing Changes, 1978; ID: 122.0077 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0077)
    - Satoru at Barre Telling Life Story #3, 1978; ID: 122.0078 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0078)
    - Satoru at Barre Telling Life Story #4, 1978; ID: 122.0079 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0079)
    - Snow Shots Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0080 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0080)
    - Snow Shots Tape #2, 1978; ID: 122.0081 (Box 126, Media ID: 122.0081)
      Alternate Title: Snow Shot and Satoru Talking
    - Snow Shot Tape #3, 1978; ID: 122.0082 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0082)
      Alternate Title: Tape 3 Reverse Pan - Last Shot
    - Snow Shot Tape #4, 1978; ID: 122.0083 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0083)
      Alternate Title: Tape 4 Rack Shots of Poster
    - Snow Shot Tape #1, 1978; ID: 122.0084 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0084)
    - Snow Shot #1, 1978; ID: 122.0085 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0085)
    - Snow Shot, 1978; ID: 122.0086 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0086)
      Alternate Title: In Satoru's Loft
    - Satoru at Kitchen #1, 1978; ID: 122.0087 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0087)
    - LFDT Performance, 1978; ID: 122.0088 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0088)
      Alternate Title: Performance - Audience
    - Painting Back drops and Setting Up, 1978; ID: 122.0089 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0089)
    - Japan House #1, 1978; ID: 122.0090 (Box 127, Media ID: 122.0090)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Outside Rehearsal
    - Japan House #2, 1978; ID: 122.0091 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0091)
      Alternate Title: Japan House Backstage
    - Japan House #3, 1978; ID: 122.0092 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0092)
      Alternate Title: Backstage, Laura, Balloons and Balloon Piece
    - Japan House #4, 1978; ID: 122.0093 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0093)
    - Japan House #5, 1978; ID: 122.0094 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0094)
      Alternate Title: Japan House #5 Backstage
    - Japan House #6, 1978; ID: 122.0095 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0095)
      Alternate Title: Japan House J. Watts, Audience, 1 & 2 Pieces
    - Japan House #7, 1978; ID: 122.0096 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0096)
      Alternate Title: Japan House - 4th Piece
    - Japan House #8, 1978; ID: 122.0097 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0097)
      Alternate Title: Japan House - 5th Piece and Audience Leaving
    - Kitchen - Satoru Shimazaki Concert #1, 1978; ID: 122.0098 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0098)
    - Kitchen - Satoru Shimazaki Concert #2, 1978; ID: 122.0099 (Box 128, Media ID: 122.0099)
      Alternate Title: 1st Dance; Geki Sei
    - Kitchen - Satoru Shimazaki Concert #3, 1978; ID: 122.0100 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0100)
      Alternate Title: "For Beauty's Nothing" Performance
    - Kitchen - Satoru Shimazaki Concert #4, 1978; ID: 121.0101 (Box 129, Media ID: 121.0101)
      Alternate Title: "Child is Father to the Man"
    - Kitchen - Satoru Shimazaki Concert #5, 1978; ID: 122.0102 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0102)
      Alternate Title: "Cakewalk" (Performance)
    - Heirlooms Reel #1, 1978; ID: 122.0103 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0103)
      Alternate Title: Documentary Act I and Intermission
    - Heirlooms Reel #2, 1978; ID: 122.0104 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0104)
      Alternate Title: Document Act I and Intermission - Act II
    - Heirlooms Document #3, 1978; ID: 122.0105 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0105)
      Alternate Title: Act I Experiment
    - Heirlooms Documentary Act III, Scene II, 1978; ID: 122.0106 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0106)
    - Heirlooms Experiment Act II, 1978; ID: 122.0107 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0107)
    - Heirlooms Experimental Act III Scene II, 1978; ID: 122.0108 (Box 129, Media ID: 122.0108)
    - a deux, 1974; ID: 122.0109 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0109)
      Alternate Title: Documentary of Rehearsal at Cubiculo
    - "Program" Ward-Nasse Gallery, 1976; ID: 122.0110 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0110)
      Duration: 40 minutes
    - "Program" Ward-Nasse Gallery - entire dance, 1976; ID: 122.0111 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0111)
    - "Program" Ward-Nasse Gallery - black and white, 1976; ID: 122.0112 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0112)
    - Spaces, 1973-1974; ID: 122.0113 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0113)
    - Wollman Hall, Tape 2, 1978; ID: 122.0114 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0114)
      Alternate Title: Ghost Shots, Wollman Hall
    - Wollman - Tape 1, 1978; ID: 122.0115 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0115)
    - Wollman Hall 1st 8 min., 3rd and last take, 1978; ID: 122.0116 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0116)
      Alternate Title: Wollman Hall
    - Wollman Hall and N.S. Dance Studio - Tape 2, 1978; ID: 122.0117 (Box 130, Media ID: 122.0117)
      Alternate Title: Spaces
    - Wollman Hall - Tape 1, Color and B/W, 1978; ID: 122.0118 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0118)
    - Wollman Hall - Tape 3, 1978; ID: 122.0119 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0119)
    - Heirlooms - Cassette 1, 1977; ID: 122.0120 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0120)
      Duration: 16 minutes
      Alternate Title: Heirlooms, Act I, no intermission
    - Heirlooms - Cassette 2, 1977; ID: 122.0121 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0121)
      Alternate Title: Heirlooms, Intermission, Act II
    - Heirlooms - Cassette 3, 1977; ID: 122.0122 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0122)
      Duration: 6 minutes
      Alternate Title: Heirlooms, Act III, Scene One - Satoru's Solo
    - Heirlooms - Cassette 4, 1977; ID: 122.0123 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0123)
      Duration: 14 minutes
      Alternate Title: Heirlooms, Act III, Scene Two
    - Heirlooms - Cassette 5, 1977; ID: 122.0124 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0124)
      Duration: Unknown
    - Heirlooms - Cassette 6, 1977; ID: 122.0125 (Box 131, Media ID: 122.0125)
    - Art/Video/Sound - Tape 1, 1979; ID: 122.0126 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0126)
    - Art/Video/Sound - Tape II, 1979; ID: 122.0127 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0127)
    - Art/Video/Sound - Tape II Original, 1979; ID: 122.0128 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0128)
    - Time Coded Woman II - Dub "J", 1981; ID: 122.0129 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0129)
      Alternate Title: Time Coded Woman II
    - Time Coded Woman II - 1st Generation Dub, 1981; ID: 122.0130 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0130)
      Alternate Title: Time Coded Woman
    - Time Coded Woman II - Dub #3, 1985; ID: 122.0131 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0131)
    - Color Laid, undated; ID: 122.0132 (Box 132, Media ID: 122.0132)
    - Laura at mirror - V-8, 1979; ID: 122.0133 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0133)
    - Laura at mirror - V-6, 1979; ID: 122.0134 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0134)
    - Glass and Shadows with Titles, 1980; ID: 122.0135 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0135)
      Orignal format: 3/4 in. Umatic
    - Editing Practice Tape, 1979; ID: 122.0136 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0136)
    - Play Tape, 1979; ID: 122.0137 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0137)
    - Dub for editing practice, 1979; ID: 122.0138 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0138)
    - First take; Laura in front of mirror - V-8, 1979; ID: 122.0139 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0139)
    - Untitled w/o metronome, 1979; ID: 122.0140 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0140)
      Alternate Title: Untitled aka Glass and Shadows aka Reflections
    - Dub of NYSCA Dub, undated; ID: 122.0141 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0141)
      Original format: 1/2 in. Open Reel
    - Assemblage Dub - Unknown Origin, undated; ID: 122.0142 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0142)
      Alternate Title: NYSCA Dub
    - Assemblage Copy - Status Unknown, undated; ID: 122.0143 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0143)
    - NySCA Sampler, 1978; ID: 122.0144 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0144)
      Alternate Title: Untitled; Heirlooms
    - Unidentified 1/2" Dub, undated; ID: 122.0146 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0146)
    - New Dub of NYSCA Untitled, 1979; ID: 122.0145 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0145)
      Alternate Title: Untitled
    - Time Coded Woman with Titles, 1980; ID: 122.0147 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0147)
    - Time Coded Woman II - Tape #9 Dub, 1980; ID: 122.0148 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0148)
    - Glass and Shadows with Titles, 1980; ID: 122.0149 (Box 133, Media ID: 122.0149)
      Alternate Title: Glass and Shadows
    - Bird House #1, Unknown; ID: 122.0150 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0150)
      Original format: Betacam
      Alternate Title: Bird House
    - Bird House #2, undated; ID: 122.0151 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0151)
    - Bird House #3, undated; ID: 122.0152 (Box 134, Media ID: 122.0152)